

Luc Nguyen Van

Personal information:

H June 05-th, 1999

210 Doi Can St, Ba Dinh, Hanoi, Vietnam

+84 375 550 576

linkedin.com/in/lucnguyen-ict

nguyenluc99.github.io

nguyenlucitbk@gmail.com

About me____

I am a computer science graduate of HUST, Vietnam. Being interested in mathematics and programming, I love researching computer algorithms. The algorithmic thinking helps me solve problems, not only in computer science and mathematics, but also in real life, more critically and efficiently. Our life would be better and more convenient with better methods and resolutions. Therefore, I enjoy researching algorithms and developing better, more efficient applications.

Skills____

C, C++

Database

Linux

Git

Java

Python

JavaScript

IAT_EX

Education

2017 – 2023 : BSc in Computer Science, HUST

Average CPA : 3.2 / 4.0

08/2020 - 01/2021: Exchange student at Uppsala University, Sweden

Language

Vietnamese : Native speaker.

English : Communicate fluently, both orally and in writing.

Awards and honors

2020 Erasmus-Mundus Scholarship 2020 for exchange student

2019 Student with "Five good merits"

Working experiences

1. Apr 2022-Present: C++ Software Engineer OJT at Toshiba Software Development Vietnam (TSDV)

- Maintain and develop multiple kinds of database Foreign Data Wrapper
- Develop data compression transfer feature to migrate data to the cloud
- 2. Mar 2021-Sep 2021: Machine Learning Engineer at Eastgate Software JSC
 - Background removal using MODNet, Mask RCNN,... .
 - OCR with Google API, NLP with nltk,... .
- 3. Jun 2019-Aug 2019: Web Developer at BigMax International Co., Ltd

Research experiences

- de Bruijn code enumeration in C++ nguyenluc99/GJ_LC_deBruijnCode (in preparation for submission).
- Dyck Path enumerations (in preparation for submission).

Teaching experiences

Introduction to Computer Science: Primary teaching assistant of two classes during office hours and lab sections. Graded assignments and gave weekly feedback. Total: 60 hours, enrollments: 80 students.

Programming techniques: Primary teaching assistant of a class during office hours and lab sections. Total: 30 hours, enrollments: 50 students.

SOFT SKILLS

- ✓ Critical thinking, persistence, responsibility and friendly
- ✓ Self-taught, work independently and in a team
- ✓ Photography

[SOCIAL ACTIVITIES]

- 2017-2022: Six-time key member and organizer of "Future career talk show" (A warmly talk between high school and university students)
- Member of some volunteering teams and activities.

(INTERESTS)

- Learn mathematics, combinatorics and graph theory
- Traveling, photography, piano, reading book, helping people
- Connect with people from other cultures, other countries and the world

FUTURE GOALS

- ⇒ Become a computer scientist and a mathematician
- Become a globally effective researcher and contributor
- ➤ Learn several more languages